ANTON SHTIPLIYSKI

WEB DEVELOPER

SKILLS:

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Javascript (ES6), React.js, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express.js, API Implementation, MySQL, Postman, Jira, Github

antonshtipliyski@yahoo.com

github.com/ahshtipliyski

linkedin.com/in/anton-shtipliyski

437-245-7861

PROFILE:

I believe that technology is breaking down barriers for us to better perform mentally, physically, and socially. From my previous experience I have proven myself to be very efficient and quick learner, even while working under pressure. Since I was a kid, I have always been keen to learn and build new things on my Computer. I love technology and I believe, that my skills will transfer over well, to become a successful Web Developer.

PROJECTS:

https://ahshtipliyski.github.io

EXPERIENCE

Reservation Sales Agent | Accor

JUL 2019 - 2020, MONCTON, NB

- Handled high volume calls on a daily basis, while making sure that the best value was presented. Worked simultaneously with few different programs.
- Built strong professional relationships with collages and management.
 Trained for management position. Problem solving on a daily basis.

Casino Supervisor | Celebrity Cruise Lines

NOV 2014 - 2018, MIAMI, FL

- Solving problems has been huge part of my daily routine. Managed up to 50 workers in Casino environment and up to 950 guests while on safety drills. Completed training for Assistant Manager.
- Handled yearly, quarterly, monthly and weekly reports. Designed and executed promotional games to bring traffic to the Casino, increased revenue by 15% on a nightly basis.
- Accountable for direct client support, to ensure complete customer satisfaction.
- Responsible for creating work schedules for staff and management.
 Evaluated employees prepared and presented appraisals. Trained staff to become supervisors and learn new games.

Casino Dealer | Carnival Cruise Lines

MAY 2012 - 2014, MIAMI, FL

- Worked under high levels of pressure with direct guest contact.
 Managed up to 10 guests at once, while making sure customer satisfaction remains number one priority.
- Performed safety drills and managed big crowds of guests.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma Candidate, Web Development

MAY 2020 - AUG 2020, TORONTO, ON

Vocational High School | Vocational Certificate / High School Diploma, Technology of Environmental Protection

SEP 2004 - 2009, Bulgaria, Sofia